Guide to the Sisterhood is Global Institute Records, 1963-2010 and undated, bulk 1980-2002 RL.01185
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1980-2001 and undated, 15 boxes
  - Women in development (Box SUBJ14)
    - The World Bank
      - Conable, Barber B.
        - Remarks on OEF International Luncheon, 1988 May 16 (Box SUBJ14)
      - Country Women in Development Strategy, undated (Box SUBJ14)
      - Population Growth and Policies in Sub-Saharan Africa, 1986 Aug. (Box SUBJ14)
      - Recent Bank and IDA Projects, 1989 Oct. (Box SUBJ14)
      - Sector Strategy Plan for The Women in Development Division, 1989 Apr. (Box SUBJ14)
      - World Bank/IMF Annual Meeting, Berlin
        - Briefing, 1988 Sept. 26 (Box SUBJ14)
      - Women in Development Country Assessment in Brief, undated (Box SUBJ14)
      - Women in Development Division
        - Ongoing projects, 1988 Sept. 21 (Box SUBJ14)
        - Listing of outputs, 1989 July 31 (Box SUBJ14)
      - Women in Development seminar report, 1989 May (Box SUBJ14)
      - World Bank Acts to Enhance the Economic Status of Asia's Women, 1988 Oct. 31 (Box SUBJ14)
  - Women's Global Film Project
    - Correspondence, 1993-1997, 2 folders (Box SUBJ14)
    - Interview transcripts, 1993-1994, 4 folders (Box SUBJ14)
  - Women's Health
    - Articles, 2001 (Box SUBJ14)
  - Women's Publications (Box SUBJ15)
    - The Feminist Press, 1989-1990 (Box SUBJ15)
    - General
      - Brochures, 1993 and undated (Box SUBJ15)
    - Women Center
      - Subscriptions, 1991 (Box SUBJ15)
  - Women's Studies
    - Proposal for the UCLA Center for the Study of Women, 1983 (Box SUBJ15)
    - Radcliff College, Henry A. Murray Research Center, 1989-1990 (Box SUBJ15)
    - Selected collection of doctoral dissertations
      - Titles, 1983-1986 (Box SUBJ15)
    - United Nations conference on women's decade in Nairobi, 1985 Aug. (Box SUBJ15)
    - Women's Studies Center
      - Bibliography, 1991 (Box SUBJ15)
    - Women's Studies, Indiana UP, 1992 (Box SUBJ15)
    - Women's Worlds: Fourth International Congress, 1990 June (Box SUBJ15)
- Organizations Series, 1978-2002 and undated, bulk 1990s-2001, 15 boxes
  Consists of materials relating to various women’s and human rights organizations. Formats include informational pamphlets and booklets, annual fund reports, newsletters, and correspondence between SIGI and members of other organizations. Significant groups of folders exist for the Association of Women in Development, the Canadian Council for Refugees, Equality Now, Feminist Majority, Isis International, the International Women's Health Coalition, the National Council for Research on Women, and the Women's Environment and Development Organization. Highlights of the series include information concerning the United Nations and some correspondence with the former First Lady, Hilary Rodham Clinton.
  The Organizations Series is organized alphabetically by organization name; Countries most represented in this series include the United States and Canada. The majority of documents are in English, with some materials in French and other languages. A few oversize materials, mostly posters have been removed to Oversize Materials.
  - Abantu for Development Training Program, 1997 Dec.- 1998 June (Box ORG1)
  - Academy for Educational Development, Request for Program Design, 1997 June 18 (Box ORG1)
  - Active Women Club, 2000 Feb. (Box ORG1)
  - Advocacy Institute 1996 Annual Report, 1996 (Box ORG1)
  - Afghan Women Council, 1997 (Box ORG1)
  - Afghan Women's Counseling and Integration Community Support Organization, 1998 Feb.- Mar. (Box ORG1)
  - Afghanistan Reconstruction Support Committee, Women's Task Force, 1998-2000 (Box ORG1)
  - African Peace Network (APNET), 1997-1998 (Box ORG1)
  - Akina Mama Wa Africa, 1995, 2001 (Box ORG1)
  - All Women's Action Society, 1998 Apr. 23 (Box ORG1)
  - American Association of University Women Educational Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box ORG1)
  - American University: Washington College of Law, 1997 Oct. 21 (Box ORG1)
  - Amideast, 1997 Apr. 10 (Box ORG1)
  - Amnesty International, 1990-1999 (Box ORG1)
  - APIK, 1996-1997 (Box ORG1)
  - Arab-American Action Network, 1997-1998 (Box ORG1)
  - Arab Association for Human Rights, 1996-1997 (Box ORG1)
  - Arab Women's Solidarity Association (AWSA), 1988-1993, 2001 (Box ORG1)
  - Asia Institute, 1993 (Box ORG1)
  - The Asia Foundation, 1996-1999 (Box ORG1)
  - Asia and Pacific Development Centre, 1997-1999 (Box ORG1)
  - Asia Pacific Forum on Women, Law, and Development, 1991-1998 (Box ORG1)
  - Asian-Pacific Resource and Research Centre for Women, 1995-1995 (Box ORG1)
  - Asian Regional Resource Center for HRE (ARRC), 2000 (Box ORG1)
  - Asian Women's Human Rights Council, 1993-1997 (Box ORG1)
  - Association for Middle East Women's Studies (AMEWS), 1996-1998 (Box ORG1)
  - L'Association quebecoise des organismes de cooperation internationale (AQOCI), Francine Nemeh, 2000-2001 (Box ORG2)
  - Association for Women in Development, 1993-1999, 3 folders (Box ORG2)
  - Ayuda, Inc. 1998 and undated (Box ORG2)
  - AWID Resource Net, 2001 Feb. 3 (Box ORG2)
  - Be Active Be Emancipated (B.A.B.E.), 1995-2001 and undated (Box ORG2)
  - Beijing + 5, 2000, 2 folders (Box ORG2)
  - Boston Women's Health Book Collective, 2000 (Box ORG2)
  - Bread and Roses, 1996-1998 and undated (Box ORG2)
  - British Council, 2000 (Box ORG2)
  - Cairo Institute, 1995-1999 and undated (Box ORG2)
  - Canadian Council for International Co-operation, Directory, 1990 (Box ORG2)
  - Canadian Council of Muslim Women, 1997-2001 and undated (Box ORG2)
  - Canadian Council for Refugees, 2000-2003, 3 folders (Box ORG3)
  - Canadian dot force Civil Society Consultation, 2001 (Box ORG3)
  - Canadian Feminist Alliance for International Action (FAFIA), 2000 (Box ORG3)
  - Canadian Human Rights Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box ORG3)
  - Canadian Research Institute for the Advancement of Women (CRIAW-ICREF), 2001 (Box ORG3)
  - Caribbean Association for Feminist Research and Action (CAFRA), 1992-2001 and undated (Box ORG3)
  - Carnegie Council on Ethics and International Affairs, Human Rights Dialogue, 1996-1998 (Box ORG3)
  - The Carter Center, 1996-1997 (Box ORG3)
  - Catholics for a Free Choice, 1998-2001 (Box ORG3)
  - Catholics for a Free Choice, call to accountability, "Sexual Exploitation of Nuns by Catholic Priests", 2001 (Box ORG3)
  - Catholics for a Free Choice, "See Change" campaign, 2000 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Global Education, 1997 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Health and Gender Equity, CHANGE, 1998-1999 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, 1995-1996 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, Jerusalem Fund, 1996-1997 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Reproductive Law and Policy, 1992-2001 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Research on Women, Wellesley College, 1998-1999 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Victims of Torture, 2000-2001 (Box ORG3)
  - Center for Women's Global Leadership, 1993-1999 (Box ORG4)
  - Center of Concern, 1992-1994 (Box ORG4)
  - Centre de Recherche d'Information et de Formation pour la Femme (CRIFF), 1999-2000 (Box ORG4)
  - Centro de Documentacion Sobre la Mujer, Peru, 1991 (Box ORG4)
  - CHANGE, 1998 and undated (Box ORG4)
  - CLADEM, Latin America and Caribbean Committee for the Defense of Women's Rights (Peru), 1990s and undated (Box ORG4)
  - Clinton, Hillary; The White House, 1996-1998 (Box ORG4)
  - Coalition for an International Criminal Court, 1996 (Box ORG4)
  - Coalition Gaie et Lesbienne, 2001 and undated (Box ORG4)
  - Coalition of Women for a Just Peace, 2001 (Box ORG4)
  - Comité canadien d'action sur le statut de la femme, 1999 (Box ORG4)
  - Committee on Gender Equity, 1997 Mar. (Box ORG4)
  - Committee to Defend Women’s Rights in the Middle East, bulletin, 2002 June (Box ORG4)
  - Conference of Non-Governmental Organizations in Consultative Relationship with the United Nations (CONGO), 1995-2000 (Box ORG4)
  - Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Discrimination Against Women (CEDAW), 2000 (Box ORG4)
  - Co-operative for Research and Education (CORE), 1997 (Box ORG4)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1996-1997 (Box ORG4)
  - Counterpart International, 1996-1997 (Box ORG4)
  - Creating Hope, Afghanistan, 1997 and undated (Box ORG4)
  - Dalit, 1995-2000 and undated (Box ORG4)
  - Dialogue on Diversity, 1993-1997 (Box ORG4)
  - Equality Now, 1992-2001, 3 of 4 folders (Box ORG4)
  - Equality Now, 1992-2001, 4 of 4 folders (Box ORG5)
  - European Network for Women's Studies, 1992-1993 (Box ORG5)
  - European Women's Lobby, 2001 (Box ORG5)
  - Federation des Femmes du Quebec, 2000-2001 (Box ORG5)
  - Feminist Majority, 1994-1998 (Box ORG5)
  - Feminist Majority, Expo 2000, 2000 (Box ORG5)
  - Feministas por la autonomia, 1999 (Box ORG5)
  - Femmes au mitan de la vie, 2001 Apr. 11 (Box ORG5)
  - Fund for Peace, 1993-1998, 2 folders (Box ORG5)
  - Gabriela- National Women's Coalition (Philippines), 1988-1993 (Box ORG5)
  - Gender Policy Review, 2000-2001 (Box ORG5)
  - General Union of Palestinian Women, 2002 (Box ORG5)
  - Global Campaign for Women's Humans Rights, undated (Box ORG5)
  - Global Fund for Women, 1999, 2000 (Box ORG5)
  - Global Stewardship Network, 1995 Aug.- Sept. (Box ORG5)
  - Graphic Network, 1996-1997 (Box ORG5)
  - Human Rights Alliance, 1999 (Box ORG5)
  - Human Rights in China (HRIC), 1995 (Box ORG5)
  - Human Rights Internet (HRI), 1999-2001 (Box ORG5)
  - Human rights, various organizations, 1980s, 2 folders (Box ORG5)
  - Human Rights Watch, 1996-1998 (Box ORG6)
  - Iansa Women, 2002 (Box ORG6)
  - Immigration and Refugee Services of America, 1997-1999 and undated (Box ORG6)
  - Institute of International Education, 1996 (Box ORG6)
  - Institute of Women's Studies, Lahore, 1997-1998 (Box ORG6)
  - Inter-African Committee on Traditional Practices, 1996-2000 (Box ORG6)
  - Interaction, 1994-1996 (Box ORG6)
  - International Association of Women Judges, 1993-1999 (Box ORG6)
  - International Centre for Criminal Law Reform and Criminal Justice Policy, 1994 (Box ORG6)
  - International Center for Human Rights and Democratic Development, 1999-2001 (Box ORG6)
  - International Center for Research on Women (ICRW), 1996-1998 (Box ORG6)
  - International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission, 1993-2000 (Box ORG6)
  - International Human Rights Documentation Network (INTERNET), 1993-1994 (Box ORG6)
  - International Institute for Sustainable Development, 1993 (Box ORG6)
  - The International Network for the Rights of Female Violence Victims in Pakistan, 1999 (Box ORG6)
  - International NGO Working Group on Refugee Women, 1994-1995 (Box ORG6)
  - International PEN Women's Writers Committee, 1995 (Box ORG6)
  - International Planned Parenthood Federation, Western Hemisphere Region Inc., 1996-1997 (Box ORG6)
  - International Rule of Law Center, 1997 June 30 (Box ORG6)
  - International Women's Health Coalition, 1992-2000, 3 folders (Box ORG6)
  - International Women's Media Foundation, 1997 June-July (Box ORG6)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch, 1986-1999, 1 of 2 folders (Box ORG6)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch, 1986-1999, 2 of 2 folders (Box ORG7)
  - International Women's Tribune Center, 1992-2001, 3 folders (Box ORG7)
  - International Women's Writing Guild, 2000 (Box ORG7)
  - Isis International
    - 1984-2000, 3 folders (Box ORG7)
    - Cross-cultural exchange, 1985 May 24 (Box ORG7)
  - Israeli Women's Network, 1997-1998 and undated (Box ORG7)
  - Kol Ha-Isha, 2002 (Box ORG7)
  - Kushandira Pamwe, 1996 (Box ORG7)
  - Laubach Literacy International, 1997 (Box ORG7)
  - Ligue democratique pour les droits de la femme, 2001 (Box ORG7)
  - Lobby europeen des femmes, 2001 and undated (Box ORG7)
  - Madre's Call to Action, 2002 (Box ORG7)
  - Manavi, 1998 and undated (Box ORG7)
  - Mahbobeh Sadria Enterprise, undated (Box ORG7)
  - Manushi, Mandu Kishmar Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box ORG7)
  - Marche mondiale des femmes, 2000-2002 (Box ORG7)
  - MESA, 1996-1997 (Box ORG7)
  - Middle East Institute, 1997-1999 (Box ORG7)
  - Millennium Forum, 2000 (Box ORG7)
  - Montreal International, 2000 Sept. (Box ORG7)
  - Ms. Magazine, Gayle Kirchenbaum correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box ORG7)
  - Muslims Against Family Violence, 1998 (Box ORG8)
  - Muslim Politics Report, 1997 Sept.-Oct. (Box ORG8)
  - Muslim women's organizations, general, 1994 and undated (Box ORG8)
  - Nari Uddug Kendra (NUK) Center for Women's Initiatives, 2000 and undated (Box ORG8)
  - National Association of Muslim Women, 1995 Feb. 23 (Box ORG8)
  - National Council for Research on Women, 1991-1996, 3 folders (Box ORG8)
  - National Institute for Citizen Education in the Law, 1994-1996 (Box ORG8)
  - National Law Center for Children and Families, 1998-1999 (Box ORG8)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1991-1992 (Box ORG8)
  - National Organization of Arab-American Women, 1993 (Box ORG8)
  - Network of East-West Women, 1993-1997 (Box ORG8)
  - Network Women's Program, Open Society Institute, 1998 (Box ORG8)
  - NGO Committee on the Status of Women, 1992-1995 (Box ORG8)
  - North American Muslim Women, 1994-1995 (Box ORG8)
  - Organisation mondiale contre la torture, 1998-1999 (Box ORG8)
  - Over the Fence, 1999 (Box ORG8)
  - The Palestine Working Women Center, undated (Box ORG8)
  - The Panos Institute, 1995-1997 (Box ORG8)
  - Parliamentarians for Global Action, 1994-1999, 2 folders (Box ORG8)
  - Peace Women, 2002 (Box ORG8)
  - Physicians for Human Rights, 1998-2002 (Box ORG8)
  - Population Crisis Committee, 1987-1993 (Box ORG8)
  - Population Reference Bureau, 1995-2000 (Box ORG9)
  - President's Interagency Council on Women, 1995-1999 (Box ORG9)
  - Pro Mujer, 1994-1999 (Box ORG9)
  - Purple Rose Campaign, 2000 and undated (Box ORG9)
  - Rape Crisis Society of Trinidad and Tobago, 1998 Sept. (Box ORG9)
  - Religious Consultation on Population, Reproductive Health and Ethics, 1995-1999 (Box ORG9)
  - Research, Action, and Information Network for the Bodily Integrity of Women, 1997 and undated (Box ORG9)
  - Revolutionary Association of the Women of Afghanistan, 2000-2001 (Box ORG9)
  - Roma Rights, 2000 (Box ORG9)
  - Search for Common Ground, 1996-2000 (Box ORG9)
  - Seeds, 1990s (Box ORG9)
  - Sexisme et droits des femmes, 2001 (Box ORG9)
  - Shirkat-Gah, 1990-1999, 2 folders (Box ORG9)
  - Simorgh Women's Resource and Publication Center, 1990s (Box ORG9)
  - Sisterhood is Global in Jordan, 2001 (Box ORG9)
  - Sisters in Islam, 1991-1999 (Box ORG9)
  - Sookmyung Women's University, Seoul, Korea, 2000 and undated (Box ORG9)
  - Rene Moawad Foundation, 1990-1997 (Box ORG9)
  - Refugee Women in Development, 1989-1998 and undated (Box ORG9)
  - Rural Women's NGO "Alga," 2001 May 17 (Box ORG9)
  - Thread, 1992 (Box ORG9)
  - United Nations
    - Center for Human Settlements, 2001 (Box ORG9)
    - UNICEF, 1993-2000 (Box ORG9)
    - Commission on Human Rights, 1995, 1997 (Box ORG9)
    - Development Fund for Women, 1988-1999, 2 folders (Box ORG10)
    - Development Program, 1990s-2001, 2 folders (Box ORG10)
    - Division for the Advancement of Women, 1996-1997 and undated (Box ORG10)
    - Economics and Social Council, 1974, 1993-1997 and undated (Box ORG10)
    - Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organizations (UNESCO), 1995-1999 (Box ORG10)
    - General, 1989, 1991, 1993 (Box ORG10)
    - Global Teaching and Learning Project, 2000 and undated (Box ORG10)
    - High Commissioner for Refugees, 1990s (Box ORG10)
    - International Research and Training Institute for the Advancement of Women (INSTRAW)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box ORG10)
      - Discussion Forum, 2002 (Box ORG10)
      - Gains Correspondence, 2001 (Box ORG10)
      - Men's Roles Seminar, 2001 (Box ORG10)
      - News, 1987-1998 (Box ORG10)
      - Newsletter, 2001-2002 (Box ORG10)
      - Violence against Women, 2001 (Box ORG10)
      - Virtual Seminar, 2002 (Box ORG10)
    - Members of the Security Council, 1990s, 2 folders (Box ORG11)
    - Non-governmental Liaison Service, 1990s, 2 folders (Box ORG11)
  - United States Agency for International Development (USAID), 1990s (Box ORG11)
  - United States Information Agency, 1998 and undated (Box ORG11)
  - United States State Department, 1998 and undated (Box ORG11)
  - Vacha Women’s Resource Center, India, undated (Box ORG11)
  - Various
    - 1997-2000, 4 folders (Box ORG11)
    - Directories of projects for women, 1978-1979 (Box ORG11)
  - Washington Office on Latin America, undated (Box ORG12)
  - Websites-Guide Star, 2001 (Box ORG12)
  - White Ribbon Campaign, 1999 and undated (Box ORG12)
  - Winrock, 1990s (Box ORG12)
  - Womankind Worldwide, undated (Box ORG12)
  - Women Envision, 1993-1995 (Box ORG12)
  - Women For a Meaningful Summit, 1988-1999 (Box ORG12)
  - Women For Mutual Security, 1993 and undated (Box ORG12)
  - Women For Women, 1998 and undated (Box ORG12)
  - Women For Women's Human Rights, 1997-1999 and undated (Box ORG12)
  - Women in Black, 2001 (Box ORG12)
  - Women Living Under Muslim Laws Network, 1992-2001 and undated, 2 folders (Box ORG12)
  - Women, Power, Politics, 1994 (Box ORG12)
  - Women Waging Peace, 1999 (Box ORG12)
  - Women's Action Network News, 2001 (Box ORG12)
  - Women's Affairs Technical Committee, 1997-1999 (Box ORG12)
  - Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children, 1991-1998, 2 folders (Box ORG12)
  - Women's Development Center Nepal, undated (Box ORG12)
  - Women's Environment and Development Center (WEDO), 1990s-2000, Folders 1-2 of 5 (Box ORG12)
  - WEDO, 1990s-2000, Folders 3-5 of 5 (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Feature Service, 1998 (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Foreign Policy Council, 1985-1988 and undated (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Foundation, 1987, 1991 and undated (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Health in Women's Hands, 1995-1996 (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Health Project, 1990-2000, 2 folders (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Institute of Freedom of the Press, undated (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Ink, 1993, 2000-2001 (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Institute for Leadership (WILD), 1996 and undated (Box ORG13)
  - Women's International Development (WID), 1985-1996 and undated (Box ORG13)
  - Women's International Net Magazine, 2000-2001 (Box ORG13)
  - Women's International Network, 2001 (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Law and Development in Africa, 1997 (Box ORG13)
  - Women's Law and Development International, 1993-1999, (2 folders) (Box ORG14)
  - Women's Learning Partnership, 2001 (Box ORG14)
  - Women's Media Circle Foundation
    - Correspondence with Anna Leah Sarabia, 1988-1998 (Box ORG14)
    - Correspondence with Marilyn Waring, 1988-1998 (Box ORG14)
  - Women's Resource Center Nepal, 1997-1999 (Box ORG14)
  - Women's Rights Network, 1997-1999 and undated (Box ORG14)
  - Women's World, 1996 and undated (Box ORG14)
  - Women's World Banking, 1990s (Box ORG14)
  - Women's World Summit Foundation, 1999-2001 and undated (Box ORG14)
  - Working Group on the Human Rights of Women, Bosnia, 1995-1997 (Box ORG14)
  - Working Group on the Ratification of the U.N. Convention on Women, 1996 (Box ORG14)
  - World Bank Women's Program, 1994-1999 (Box ORG14)
  - World Federalist Association, Minerva Magazine, 2000-2001 (Box ORG14)
  - World Organization of Iranian Women "Solidarity," 1992-1993 (Box ORG14)
  - World Water Vision, 2000, (2 folders) (Box ORG15)
  - Worldwatch Institute, 1990-1994 (Box ORG15)
  - Worldwide News, 1992-1993 (Box ORG15)
  - Yokohama Women's Forum, 1990-2001 (Box ORG15)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 1993 (Box ORG15)
- Geographical Files Series, 1963-2001 and undated, 13 boxes
  Contains materials relating to women’s rights and socio-economic conditions in numerous countries and regions around the world. Materials include articles from newspapers and magazines, published statements, pamphlets, magazines, symposia reports, and government-published reports on women and women’s rights within particular countries. There are a large number of newsletters in this series, many self-published by local women’s groups, as well as some e-mails and other correspondence. Topics concern women’s rights, abortion rights, reproductive health, rape and violence against women and girls, notable women in politics, prostitution and sex tourism, women and the Israel/Palestine peace conflict, women and the family, and women in the workforce. Highlights of the series are campaign materials and personal correspondence for Paula DiPerna (United States), and an unpublished manuscript of a book commemorating the Montreal massacres of 1989 (Canada).
  The folders are organized alphabetically by country, continent, or region; materials within are in original order, which is sometimes chronological. In some instances there are folders for both continents and countries (for example, there are folders for Africa as well as Zimbabwe). Countries most represented are Pakistan, the Philippines, and Malaysia. The majority of the materials in the series is in English, with some exceptions written in the language of the country. There are a significant number of items in this series, mainly newspapers, that have been re-housed in Oversize Materials.
  - Afghanistan (Box GEO1)
    - Afghan women, 1998-2000 (Box GEO1)
    - Afghan women human rights, 1996-2001, 1-11 of 12 folders (Box GEO1)
    - Afghan women human rights, 1996-2001, 12 of 12 folders (Box GEO2)
    - Women for Women Afghanistan, circa 2000 (Box GEO2)
  - Africa
    - Draft protocol to African charter on human and peoples' rights on the rights of women in Africa, 2001 May (Box GEO2)
    - Femnet, 2001 (Box GEO2)
    - General, 1984-1990, 2 folders (Box GEO2)
    - Kabissa-fahamu newsletters, 2001 May-June (Box GEO2)
    - Women's rights, 1990s-2001 (Box GEO2)
  - Albania
    - Albania stands against winds of change, undated (Box GEO2)
  - Arabic World
    - 1980-1992 (Box GEO2)
  - Algeria
    - 1995-1999 (Box GEO2)
  - Asia
    - 1980s and undated (Box GEO2)
  - Australia (Box GEO3)
    - 1989-1993, 2 folders (Box GEO3)
  - Austria
    - 1975-1985 (Box GEO3)
  - Azerbaijan
    - Appeal for solidarity and support for women demonstrators, 2000 (Box GEO3)
  - Bahrain
    - Amnesty International: women and children subject to increasing abuse, 1996 (Box GEO3)
  - Baltics
    - Baltic UN-NGO consultation on women, 1995 Dec. 8-10 (Box GEO3)
  - Bangladesh
    - 1981-1989 and undated (Box GEO3)
  - Bangladesh
    - 1986-2001, 2 folders (Box GEO3)
  - Belgium
    - 1972-1979 (Box GEO3)
  - Bosnia/Croatia
    - 1993-2001 (Box GEO3)
    - A petition concerning Bosnia-Herzegovina, 1993 (Box GEO4)
  - Botswana
    - Government to address to discrimination of women, 1999 (Box GEO4)
  - Brazil
    - 1984-1991 and undated, 2 folders (Box GEO4)
  - Bulgaria
    - 1983-1999 (Box GEO4)
  - Burma
    - 1989, 2001 (Box GEO4)
  - Cambodia
    - 1975-1989, 1997 (Box GEO4)
  - Canada
    - 1984-1990 and undated (Box GEO4)
    - Quebec, 1991-2000 (Box GEO4)
  - Caribbean
    - 1981-1994 (Box GEO4)
    - 1984-1991 (Box GEO5)
  - Central Asia
    - 1997 (Box GEO5)
  - Chile
    - Protest for the disappeared, 1990 Jan. 22 (Box GEO5)
  - China
    - 1964, 1983-1992 (Box GEO5)
  - Colombia
    - Colombians turning to men for birth control, 1988 Apr. 13 (Box GEO5)
  - Costa Rica
    - Law for the promotion of equality for women in Costa Rica, undated (Box GEO5)
  - Czechoslovakia
    - Social certainties in Czechoslovakia, 1982; Czechoslovakia, yesterday and today, 1985 (Box GEO5)
  - Denmark
    - 1984-1989 (Box GEO5)
  - Eastern Europe/Central Asia
    - 1997-2001 (Box GEO5)
  - Egypt
    - 1989-1998 and undated (Box GEO5)
  - Egypt
    - 1999-2001 (Box GEO5)
  - El Salvador
    - 1985-1990 and undated (Box GEO5)
  - England
    - 1989-1990 and undated (Box GEO5)
  - Ethiopia
    - 1980-1986 (Box GEO5)
  - Europe, General
    - 1990-1996 (Box GEO5)
  - Fiji
    - 1989-1992 and undated (Box GEO5)
  - Finland
    - 1975 (Box GEO5)
  - France